You are particularly interested in extremes:
Microscopic organisms that live under extreme conditions-
-like the ice on Antarctic or inside volcanoes.
These environments are similar to those on other planets, such as Mars.
It is important partly to understand how life has arisen on our planet-
-And what conditions we have to colonize other celestial bodies.
Some day our own planet will be swallowed by the universe again.
It can be through an asteroid, as on the time of dinosaurs-
-or that the sun goes out.
No man has yet set foot on Mars, the race is underway.
Natuschka Lee is researching the European Space Organization Esa-
-It to demonstrate life in space in general and Mars in particular-
-Ope which life from the earth can survive there.
We have sent different organisms to the space station.
There have been extreme bacteria, fungi, lichens and mosses.
They have been sitting on a container that we attached outside the space station.
Then they have been allowed to circulate around the earth for 1.5 years.
So we hope to simulate how organisms from the earth can react-
-Or genuine space conditions, e.g.
If they ended up on Mars.
Many survived cosmic radiation-